Siddharth Vishwakarma

Kanpur Nagar, Uttar Pradesh, India



siddharth.vishwakarma@hotmail.com



8707765882



linkedin.com/in/mrsiddharthvishwakarma

Summary

I am passionate web development enthusiast on a mission to craft digital experiences that captivate and engage. My journey into the world of code began with a spark of curiosity, and it has evolved into a fervent dedication to mastering the art of web development.

With a strong foundation in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, I have the power to bring concepts to life through visually appealing and interactive websites.

Experience

Web Developer

TechnoHacks EduTech Official Sep 2023 - Present (1 month)

Web Developer

CodeClause Sep 2023 - Present (1 month)

Web Developer

CodSoft

Aug 2023 - Sep 2023 (2 months)

Education



Axis Colleges

Bachelor of Computer Application(BCA) Aug 2021 - Present

Central Board of Secondary Education

Intermediate, Commerce

Central Board of Secondary Education

High School

Licenses & Certifications



in Python for Students - LinkedIn

- Python vs. JavaScript for Development LinkedIn
- Microsoft 365: Choose the Right Tool for the Job LinkedIn
- in How to Highlight Your Job Skills LinkedIn
- Sololearn (Sololearn
- in Ethical Hacking: System Hacking LinkedIn
- in HTML Essential Training LinkedIn
- © Celonis Foundations Celonis
- MongoDB Basics ICT Academy Learnathon MongoDB MDB8ep891zrx4
- © Get Data into the EMS Celonis
- IT Academy: Cloud and Virtualization Concepts VMware
- Automation Anywhere Certified Advanced RPA Professional UiPath
- Database Management System Science Graduates Infosys Springboard
- AWS Academy Graduate AWS Academy Cloud Security Foundations Amazon Web Services (AWS)
- Computer Vision Onramp MathWorks

Skills

Database Management System (DBMS) • Robotic Process Automation (RPA) • Automation • MongoDB • Web Development • C (Programming Language) • Python (Programming Language) • C++ • Java • SQL